Finding Aid for John Tanton Papers 1960-2007
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Conservation Organizations and Issues
  - Correspondence 1971-1992 scattered (Box 25)
  - Dam Construction
    - Correspondence 1971-1977, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Dam Study Committee 1977-1982, 1985, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Dam Study Committee survey 1982, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Dam construction regulations 1968-1983 scattered (Box 25)
  - Emmet County Sanitary Code, miscellaneous material 1981-1983 (Box 25)
  - Energy: Miscellaneous material 1980-1983 (Box 25)
  - Three Fires Pointe
    - Environmental assessment 1988 (Box 25)
    - Research and memoranda 1990-1993, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Sierra Club, Michigan Chapter 1970-1972 (Box 25)
  - Newspaper clippings 1981-1995 scattered, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and news articles 1968-2006 scattered (Folder 1)